Kay Davis Designer + front-end developer

About me

I am a seasoned UX/UI designer with over 12 years experience designing websites and applications for some of the worlds most loved brands. Most recently I spent the last year learning front-end development through the University of Washington's full-stack bootcamp program.

My passion is to create simple, delightful experiences that are universally accessible to all, that scale across platforms, feeling natural on any device.

Experience

Principal Design Manager - Design Systems / Microsoft Teams 2020 - Current

Senior Design Manager - Design Systems / Microsoft Teams 2019 - 2020

Senior Interaction Designer - Skype [Microsoft] 2017 - 2019

Product Designer - Microsoft Windows 2017 - 2017

Interaction Designer - Skype [Microsoft] 2015 - 2017

Experience Design Manager - LEGO.com & Consumer Experiences 2015 - 2015

Creative Lead - LEGO.com & Consumer Experiences 2012 - 2015

Senior UX Designer - LEGO Consumer Insights & Experience Innovation 2011 - 2012

Experience Designer - LEGO Consumer Insights & Experience Innovation 2009 - 2011

Education

University of Washington Full-Stack Developer Certification 2020 - 2021

Ravensbourne College of Design and Communication BA (Hons) Graphic Design 2005 - 2009

Contact

Phone

+1 206 501 0230

Email

kaydavis21@googlemail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kayleighdavis/

Github

https://github.com/FAC-73

Portfolio

https://fac-73.github.io/lost-sirens/

Skills

HTML
CSS
Javascript
Jquery
Node.js

Design

UX & UI
Information Architecture
Systems / Component design
Typography

Tools + Prototyping

Figma
Sketch
Adobe XD
Axure Pro
Tumult Hype
Final Cut Pro
Adobe AfterEffects

Conferences & publications

UX London 2015
Guest speaker
"My tablet is my Teddy - how understanding children can

Universal Methods of Design "LEGO Experience design wheel"

help you design for everyone"